(Penny(arriving):)What's...
?
(Sheldon:)Your characterization of
(Sheldon:)approximately 171 different men
as "a few."
(Penny(arriving):)What...
(Penny:)Where did you
get 171 men?
(Sheldon:)Simple extrapolation.
(Sheldon:)In the three years
that I've known you,
(Sheldon:)you were single for two.
(Sheldon:)During that time,
I saw 17 different suitors.
(Sheldon:)If we work backwards,
correcting for observation bias
(Sheldon:)and postulate an initial
dating age of 15...
(Penny:)Whoa, wait,
wait, wait.
(Penny:)I did not start dating at 15.
I'm sorry. Sixteen?
Fourteen.
(Sheldon:)My mistake.
(Sheldon:)Now, assuming the left side
of a bell curve
(Sheldon:)peaking around the present,
that would bring the total
(Sheldon:)up to 193 men.
(Sheldon:)Plus or minus eight men.
(Amy:)Remarkable.
(Amy:)Did you have sexual intercourse
with all of these men?
(Howard:)No.
(Sheldon:)Although that number would be
(Sheldon:)fairly easy
to calculate.
Oh.
(Sheldon:)Based on the number of
awkward encounters I've had